

SKILLS

SOFTWARES

Final Cut Pro Adobe Premiere Pro Adobe After Effects Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom

AREAS OF INTEREST

Cinematography
Photography
Art Direction
Editing
Grading
Direction

PORTFOLIO

Behance

https://www.behance.net/nandunath

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Malaylam

NANDUNATH K V

VISUAL STORY TELLER

I am a self taught, engineer turned, enthusiastic cinematographer cum video editor upholds five years of experience on crafting the films with a unique way of tailoring. The passion I follow makes me keen observative, creative and innovative on story telling, content creation, filming and tailoring the visuals with with an ability to coordinate a diverse spectrum of projects and team members. My eyes are always peeled for the next project that will further challenge and master my skills since it is not a job for me but what I love.

EXPERIENCE

Video Editor | Videographer | Creative Director June 2022- Present

INFIJOY- Integrated well being platform

- Created the story board for trailers of courses adapting current social media marketing scenario.
- Edited and curated the trailers, intro sequences and masterclasses of various courses that platform provides.
- Shot and organized the course filming in a well scheduled time plan by making all the necessary resources available on time and beneficial.
- Organized footages and working files in a centralized and creative way to make it easier and futuristic in further times.
- Played a major role in marketing as we bring the course and content to people who really needed.
- Edited various types social media content like reels, shorts, snippets, sneeakpeaks, shoery testimonial, etc without losing the aim of the content.

CONTACT



nandu.nandu.nath1@gmail.co m



Creative head- Chief Editor I Lead Cinematographer | January 2017- June 2022

Purple Bokeh Wedding Photogaphy and cinematography

- Crafted 250+ films and shot 500+ events during the period at Purple bokeh
- Coordinated the team of video editors and designers with aspects of aesthetics and technicality by making a healthy atmosphere
- Gained the skill of sensing the latest marketing trends on videos
- Maintained the quality and dignity of the company by delivering the standard and customised output to the clients on time.

Freelance Cinematographer - Video Editor | 2017-Present

• Shot and edited couple of advertisement videos of some renowned brands.

EDUCATION

Uniiversity of calicut

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science Engineering 2013/2017

Indhira Gandhi National Open University

Functional English And Soft skills 2010/2011